Bronson Price Papers 1926-1978 Mss.Ms.Coll.16
American Philosophical Society
- Series IV. Photographs, 1948
  35mm slides taken by Laurence Snyder at the 8th International Congress of Genetics held in Stockholm. Included are informal images of Richard B. Goldschmidt, Theodosius Dobzhansky, G. Ledyard Stebbins, Sheldon C. Reed, Bentley Glass, J. B. S. Haldane, R. A. Fisher, Herman J. Muller, C. D. Darlington, George Shull, Hans Nachtsheim, and others. There are approximately 15 touristic photos of Stockholm and vicinity, including two pictures of Linnaeus's house in Uppsala.
  - Goldschmidt, Dobzhansky, Stebbins, Bryson, Smith, Reed, 1
    Aboard ship
  - Dobzhansky, Stebbins, Dr. and Mrs. Glass, 2
  - Theodosius Dobzhansky, 3
  - J.B.S. Haldane, Turpin, 4
  - R. A. Fisher, 5
    Portrait, standing in front of sign for Eighth International Congress of Genetics
  - Muller, 6
  - J. B. S. Haldane, Guldborg, 7
  - Waardenburg, Francheschetti, 8
  - Darlington, Kemp, 9
  - Dr. and Mrs. Shull, Guldborg, 10
  - Race and Wilner, 11
  - Glass, Wolff, 12
  - Sjogren, Nachtsheim, Böök, 13
  - Group on Gripsholm, 14
    Geneticists aboard ship; see also #21
  - Fisher, Ford, Finney, Riddell, 15
    Seated at table, eating lunch
  - Hanhart, Stockholm, 16
  - Goldschmidt, Reed, Stebbins, 17
  - Reed, Mrs. Price, Mrs. Claussen, Shull, Guldborg, Keeler, 18
  - Dr. and Mrs. Glass, Mrs. Bishop, Guldborg, Boyden, 19
  - Boyden, Hull, Glass, Reed, 20
  - Group on Gripsholm, 21
    Geneticists aboard ship; see also #14
  - View in Stockholm: Old City, 22
  - City Hall, Stockholm, from Old City, 23
  - Kristin Bonnevie, 24
  - King's Summer Palace, Stockholm, 25
  - En route to Drottingholm, 26
    View of small sailboat
  - Boat to Drottingholm, 27
    View of ferry deck
  - Dahlberg's Inst., Uppsala, 20
    Exterior view
  - Linnaeus's home, Uppsala, 29
    Exterior view, over garden
  - Sod roof at Linnaeus's home, 30
  - Medborgarhuset, 31
  - Karolinska Institutet, Stockholm, 32
  - Stockholm, from Sveavägen looking down Kungsgatan, 33
  - Stockholm, from Grand Hotel toward Royal Castle, 34
  - Stockholm, 35
    General view of wharf
  - Looking aft on Gripsholm, 36
  - Looking forward on Gripsholm, 37